{
  "registeredUsers": [
    {
      "email": "aaa",
      "password": "aaa",
      "cpassword": "aaa",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "email": "abc@gmail.com",
      "password": "abc",
      "cpassword": "abc",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "email": "qqq@gmail.com",
      "password": "qqq",
      "cpassword": "qqq",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "1. AngularJS is a ____?",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. Java Framework"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. Javascript Framework",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "C. HTML Framework"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. SQL Framework"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: B) AngularJS is a JavaScript framework."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2. AngularJS is perfect for?",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. MPAs"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. DPAs"
        },
        {
          "text": "C. CPAs"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. SPAs",
          "correct": true
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: D) AngularJS is perfect for SPAs."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3. Choose the reactor which is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS.",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. ng-bind directives",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "B. ng-model directives"
        },
        {
          "text": "C. ng-init directives"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. ng-app directives"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: A) ng-bind directive is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4. Choose the correct syntax for writing AngularJS expression.",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. [expression]"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. {{expressions}}",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "C. {{{expressions}}}"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. {expressions}"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: B) {{expressions}} is the correct syntax."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5. Choose the advantage of Angular JS among the following.",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. it provides reusable components"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. it uses dependancy injection and makes use of sepration of concerns"
        },
        {
          "text": "C. it is unit-testable"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. all of the above",
          "correct": true
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: D) All of the above advantages of Angular JS"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6. Choose the incorrect AngularJS filter.",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. orderby"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. email",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "C. currency"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. lowercase"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: B) email is not an AngularJS filter."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7. Who is the father of AngularJS?",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. Misko Hevery",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "B. Brad Green"
        },
        {
          "text": "C. Mike Adams"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. Adam Bronze"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: A) Misko Hevery is the father of AngularJS."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8. The total $RootScope an AngularJS application can have is?",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. 0"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. 1",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "C. 2"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. 3"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer:  B) Total $RootScope an AngularJS application can have is 1."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9. Among the following which can be used to write AngularJS directives",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. Attribute"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. Class Name"
        },
        {
          "text": "C. Tag"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. All of the above",
          "correct": true
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: D) All of the above can be used to write the AngularJS directives."
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10. Among the following choose the one which is responsible for the startup of the angular 2 projects.",
      "options": [
        {
          "text": "A. app.ts"
        },
        {
          "text": "B. main.ts",
          "correct": true
        },
        {
          "text": "C. index.js"
        },
        {
          "text": "D. angular.cli.json"
        }
      ],
      "explanation": "Answer: B) main.ts is Responsible for the startup of the angular 2 project"
    }
  ]
}